Content is currency
And the driving force behind successful apps and experiences
But it's becoming harder for businesses to keep pace at a vast world of innovative content
Adaptive Cards provide a flexible JSON based schema that's beautiful by default
empowering you to be open to any content.
As a purely declarative solution Adaptive Cards provide the performance and security you need to deliver engaging experiences.
Native renderers for all major platforms ensure your content comes across fast and fluid.
With built-in separation of layout and styling integration is easy and bringing fresh new content faster than ever from an ever growing network of providers
All built on open source and open development practices, enabling innovation that benefits everyone.
Adaptive Cards give you effortless and endless possibilities to shape the future of your experiences
Open yourself up to content with Adaptive Cards